It's time for the Push-Door Supply Station, isn't it?
The last time it's open for business.
It's the final episode.
I lost my appetite when you said it's the last time.
Okay, if you can't eat it, I'll eat it for you.
This is super delicious.
Crispy Lettuce Stem
This one's going to be really tasty.
Do we just eat it straight?
Yeah.
You'll definitely love this.
This is a bit like our
Wuxi-style Sweet and Sour Ribs.
I'm telling you,
having all this green onion and garlic,
this sauce is amazing.
I'm telling you,
this is unbeatable.
This afternoon during the investigation,
well,
later, if you have a solo mission,
where you need to find someone,
let me tell you who to get.
Him.
He's the bravest.
Ask him to go with you.
He's a bit bolder.
He is extremely brave.
You guys are cracking me up.
You play Valorant too?
I play Valorant too.
Really?
Do you play often?
I literally just learned how to play.
Are you on set these days?
Not lately.
Let's play together when I get back.
I really can't find this key evidence.
You actually expect to find the key evidence?
So naive.
Really, you're too...
too young.
Right, we also have something
called key evidence.
What's that?
It means once you find that thing,
you can lock in the killer immediately.
Lock in the killer immediately?
You'll know who did it.
So what are we doing next?
What are we doing next?
A second search after we finish eating.
Later, if you have a solo mission,
where you need to find someone,
let me tell you who to get.
Him.
He's the bravest.
Right.
Ask him to go with you.
He's a bit bolder.
He can protect you.
He is extremely brave.
You guys are cracking me up.
Do you know why his hand is injured?
He got hurt fighting that ghost.
I check the trending topics too, you know!
Hurry up.
This is really boring.
Because during my student days,
I was always a third wheel for couples.
Really?
And here I thought the boy liked me.
Turns out,
no wonder he was always looking my way!
Exactly.
I want some too.
This is really good.
Shall I peel it for you?
No thanks, I'll do it myself.
Let me try some.
I'll peel it for you.
I'll do it.
Delicious.
Working until 11 PM...
and still going home to play a few games.
What are...
What game do you play?
Honor of Kings.
There's no escape!
Mai Shiranui uses Flash to dash up,
and pushes directly with her ultimate.
Then follows up with a beautiful finish,
and even takes down Fu Longfei in the end.
Honor of Kings.
You play Valorant too?
I play Valorant too.
Really?
Do you play often?
I know how to play.
I literally just learned how to play.
Are you on set these days?
Not lately.
Let's play together when I get back.
I'm no good.
I'm a huge noob.
Let him teach you.
He'll teach you.
He's really good.
A huge noob.
It's fine.
He'll carry you.
I'm a noob too.
They said August is the anniversary.
Right.
When I was shooting my last project,
a coach came to the set to teach me.
A coach?
Yeah.
You even got a coach?
The game provided the coach for me.
I've already learned it.
I even played in an exhibition match.
I played an exhibition match in Hangzhou.
Played really well.
My aiming is pretty good.
I just don't know how to use the items.
I don't know how.
It's all so confusing.
I can only aim.
It's okay, just for fun.
Where's Ke?
He went to reshoot the killer's crime process.
He went to the bathroom.
Alright, friends.
Let's go.
It's time for the Push-Door Supply Station, isn't it?
And today is
the last time it's open for business.
What do you mean by last time it's open?
It's the final episode.
We won't have this little dining table anymore.
What's going on?
I'm gonna miss it.
I lost my appetite when you said it's the last time.
Okay, if you can't eat it, I'll eat it for you.
No problem.
We can all help you eat it.
We're all starving.
It's the final episode of Push-Door Supply Station.
We probably won't have the chance to come here anymore.
So whatever money is on the card,
let's spend it all at once.
So we're not eating tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow's meal won't be from the Supply Station.
We have to buy things from the Supply Station ourselves.
Who is this?
What is this?
Swiped the card.
I thought you were grabbing something.
You really are...
Swiped the card.
The two detectives aren't doing their jobs.
Not doing your jobs, what are you doing here?
Did someone swipe?
Where's my meal card?
Okay, swiped successfully.
It's a success, everyone. It's a success.
You don't need to fight for it.
Your money will definitely be enough today.
We still have our savings from last time.
Right.
I swiped so many today.
How do I have so many?
Bro.
Do you know why--
Wait, look.
Why do some people have zero stamina?
This obviously isn't about lacking ability.
It's clearly because...
we're focused on solving cases.
Right. First, we're active in solving cases.
Second is...
we hope everyone...
enjoys swiping the meal cards.
Exactly.
Another display of selflessness.
Of course.
Right.
Making excuses for yourself again.
Why do you two have zero stamina?
Because the two of us...
are always the main force...
when it comes to investigating.
Investigating.
And when we see meal cards,
we let our teammates swipe them.
We never swipe them ourselves.
Right.
Are you like that too?
Let's look at the footage.
Bro, here's another one.
There's another one back here.
Come on!
You're ordering me around like this?
Ding, Ding Buding!
I love you so much!
Yeah.
It's kind of like...
failing to get into Tsinghua University
and saying I was making room for others.
Thank you.
I guess I should thank you.
Right.
What about first and second place?
First and second place are usually...
really strong.
Their ability to find meal cards...
is very strong.
Yes.
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for the next sentence.
What about the one in the middle?
Singling me out?
It's always like this.
I work really hard here too.
The situation in the middle is...
a bit special.
Right, a bit more special.
Okay, so here's the thing.
Now our Xiao Ding is basically...
the big boss, right?
Yeah.
Big Boss Ding.
Big Boss.
You're a boss too.
I'm the second brother.
Second brother.
And she's the third sister.
Big brother won't judge second brother.
You two are both my good brothers.
What about me?
Let's see what we have today.
Alright?
It's useless to keep it anyway.
It's our last time.
Let's spend it all.
Okay.
First, there's the Push Deluxe Set.
We have to order this, right?
A must-order. Come on, big bro.
Didn't you calculate the total earlier?
You guys...
Ordering one of everything should be enough.
1,300 plus 400 plus 200...
1,980.
(Under) 2,000.
Then we can't order everything.
Actually, ordering four...
Almost...
...should be about right.
I want the Deluxe.
The Deluxe is a must-order, okay?
Okay.
Let's not waste time.
Who has money?
You do, Ding.
Ding, my bro.
Come on, order it.
Sure.
We definitely have to order it.
You guys earned all of this.
Little Ding-bao.
I don't even want them myself.
Just tell me if you're treating me or not.
Then one 800...
...and three 300s.
Can we choose?
Can those without money choose?
Yes.
What do you want?
I want the Fired Up.
Because I feel like it's spicy.
Fired Up is skewers.
Fiery Hot is the spicy one.
Then I want Fiery Hot.
Sure.
Okay.
Then what is "Su"?
Push Su.
Suzhou cuisine.
Is it possible...
Suzhou cuisine. It's possible.
Suzhou cuisine is delicious.
What kind of food is it mostly?
Sweet dishes.
Right, Jiangsu and Zhejiang cuisine.
Let's try it since we're in Suzhou, okay?
Okay.
Sure.
Then we'll get one Deluxe...
...one Fiery Hot...
...and one Push Su.
Perfect.
Sounds good.
Let's get a bit more.
No, wait, we still have some.
We have some balance left.
We can get that...
The Deluxe, Push Su, Fiery Hot...
...plus a Sweet one.
We can use it all up and have them send water.
Sure.
Right, they'll give us some water if we use it all.
For the final service of Push-Door Supply Station...
...the system is giving out bonuses.
Drinks are complimentary with the meals.
Players may enjoy the food to their heart's content.
Serve it up, come on.
What's this?
Mini hotpot.
Nice.
You love spicy food, right?
Yes.
Where are you from?
I'm from Wenzhou.
Wenzhou.
Can people from Wenzhou eat spicy food?
Really nice.
Well then...
This is way too luxurious.
Over 200 kinds of dishes.
Let's see if there are any duplicates.
I'll bring them over to you.
There's no blood.
I can't eat blood.
Chicken blood, duck blood.
Nan doesn't eat that.
Alright, next up is Push Fiery Hot.
I want some of that too.
Here you go.
Thanks, babe.
So good.
Is it really that good?
So satisfying.
Is this how mermaids eat?
This tastes like the snacks outside school.
Really?
Pass some over.
Here.
You... let me open it for you.
It's not that I don't want to open it.
I really can't do it with one hand.
I'll open it for you.
Hand it over.
Is this a jianbing rolled with scallions?
Yes.
This is Suzhou cuisine.
Jianbing rolled with scallions.
Shandong cuisine.
Wait, guys.
We can do this.
Wrap a skewer in it.
Wrap a skewer.
Zibo.
Right, Zibo barbecue.
Big bro really knows how to eat.
Do you guys want this jianbing?
I want a jianbing too.
It's stuck together quite...
Here, give this to me.
I'll tear off another one for you.
I think we can wrap some skewers in it.
Wrap a sausage.
After eating the scallion...
When we talk this afternoon...
Will that be okay?
If you're the only one eating it...
We all have to eat it.
That way, we won't think each other stinks.
Really?
Yeah.
So what if you think I stink?
Would you think I stink?
I wouldn't.
This scallion is so good.
Scallion...
Jianbing rolled with scallions.
Try some.
There's another pot.
Soup.
What kind of soup is this?
Is it bone broth?
Should be.
This is really a feast.
Bros.
You guys are so nice.
This food...
This is delicious.
Try this.
See if it's cooked.
Definitely.
Ready to eat.
The meat is ready to eat.
Do you guys normally eat this well?
Only when you're here
do we eat this well.
It's fine.
Do you want sesame paste or peanut butter?
I just want vinegar.
Okay.
Thanks, babe.
There is no vinegar, babe.
I'll just eat it plain then.
What's with you guys calling everyone "babe"?
She likes calling people "babe".
Here's the thing.
Brother Ning.
When you livestream, you call them...
"Fam."
"Fam," "friends."
But for us...
We also...
Sometimes we also use "babe."
You call your fans "babe"?
Each other.
Okay.
Me too.
Call them what?
Babe.
Wait.
What do you call your fans?
"Friends," "fam."
We called them "bros" before.
You...
What about you?
"Babes."
"Babies."
You call them "babies"?
Never heard that, right?
Never heard it.
You even call me...
What?
I said...
He said "never heard that, right?"
I said I haven't.
He just calls me...
I'm telling you,
having all this green onion and garlic,
this sauce is amazing.
I'm telling you,
this is unbeatable.
Unbeatable.
This afternoon during the investigation,
well...
Some of the meat was just put in.
The meat, right?
This is ready to eat.
Yeah.
This is ready.
It was already cooked.
You're pouring for us, huh?
Yeah.
Thanks.
You're so nice.
Here.
Thanks.
Look at your friend.
I have to give her a chance to shine.
You know?
You think I didn't want to do it?
This is yours.
Thanks.
Okay, no worries.
Just take care of yourself.
It's fine, just two cups left.
It's okay.
Such a caring sweetheart.
Seriously.
Really, she's great.
Always spots what needs doing.
Really.
You've got yours too.
Got it.
Everyone has one.
Good.
Thanks.
Have we video-called before?
Yes.
Because of the director, right?
Yeah.
The director must really like you.
Are you guys done shooting that show?
We are.
We just wrapped a month ago.
What do you mean?
Did they want you for it back then?
No.
We also worked on a project together.
Director Huang Tianren.
We worked with the same director.
The director wanted you guys to meet.
Yeah.
When they had their kick-off dinner,
they video-called me.
And as soon as I picked up,
her face popped up.
We just...
But our cast often gets together.
We get along pretty well.
Was it that movie of yours?
A drama series.
Do you know that for a while,
those set photos of you and Bai...
we were forwarding them like crazy in our group.
When you were shooting that show with Bai Yu,
we'd share in our group chat every day...
set photos of you two.
Bai is super nice.
Yeah.
He's great.
So, you mean...
After you finished shooting that show with Bai,
you shot that movie with Jin?
Yeah.
Back then, Jin Jing...
We even talked about this show.
When we were singing...
We hadn't worked together yet, right?
We had.
You practiced that song on set every day.
"Emotionally shattered."
You said the vocal coach told you to sing it like that.
Shattered, like that.
Practicing every day.
You were there too, right?
He was.
I was.
I saw you guys sing it.
Really.
With your hair dyed red.
What gig was this?
The New Year's Eve gala.
You dyed your hair red.
Can you dye your hair red now?
No.
I have to spray it black.
It's the last episode of Push-Door Supply Station.
My friends.
It really went by so fast.
I'm so sad.
Whenever we record this show
back-to-back, it's like this.
It's just over in a flash.
Right.
Yeah. You can't say it was fast this year,
but it just felt
pretty rushed, I think.
The first time, we recorded for four days.
The second time was three days.
This time, we finished it all at once.
Are you happy, Ding,
to join our big family?
Happy.
Happy and joyful.
Ask me.
Are you happy, Ning?
Not happy.
I hate it so much.
That's not a valid answer.
Mostly because I haven't done this type before,
I find it very interesting.
In this kind of setting,
everyone bonds extremely fast.
Right, we get closer so fast.
And it feels like you can quickly,
like, really quickly,
just blend right in.
Does it feel good?
It feels pretty good.
Did you get that feeling
of the thrill of acting like you wanted?
You really want to take him to Hengdian.
Because none of us go to Hengdian anymore.
Right?
Do I?
Hasn't he acted before?
"A Writer's Odyssey 2."
You're in it, right?
Yeah, an older one.
He always wants them to go to Hengdian
to act with him.
That's great. It's a good thing.
Learn from your older brother Keyu.
Can you not...
Why are you here?
Younger brother Keyu.
Learn from your younger brother Keyu.
Learn more from your older brother Zhang.
Learn more from your older brother Ning.
You have to learn from everyone.
Learn from all of them.
This is super delicious.
Crispy Lettuce Stem.
Can you not reach it?
Let me push it over.
I can reach it.
This is going to be very tasty.
Do we just eat it straight?
Yeah.
You'll definitely love this.
This is a bit like our
Wuxi-style Sweet and Sour Ribs.
Ribs.
You guys should have one.
Want some Wuxi-style Sweet and Sour Ribs?
I'll eat it later.
I'll get it myself.
Thank you.
It's definitely delicious.
Fragmented emotions
Scenes of your world
I'm going on the 26th.
Going to his (Jay Chou's) concert.
The 26th this year?
Yeah.
Later this month.
Jay Chou?
Where?
Beijing.
Is it a new tour?
Probably.
Are you guys still holding it this year?
Soon.
Very soon.
Early August.
All over the country?
No.
Just two locations.
And we also have a family sports meet.
Yeah.
We're holding a family sports meet too.
Are you actually competing in sports?
Yeah, sports competitions.
Like what kind of sports?
Basketball, soccer, archery, high jump.
And obstacle courses.
Similar to "Super Nova Games".
Pretty similar.
But it's just for your own family.
Yeah, just our family.
Have you ever participated in "Super Nova Games"?
I have.
What were your events?
Archery.
Fencing...
Shooting.
You participated in a lot then.
Do they still hold it?
"Super Nova Games"?
I don't know.
I only went once.
I even won a gold medal.
A gold medal in fencing.
That's so cool.
If we were to hold one, it'd be...
Super hilarious.
What kind of meet could we even hold?
What kind of sports could we even do?
Let's play it safe.
Take it easy, all of us.
Eat that tofu.
What do you want to eat?
I'll get it for you.
You should have some sesame paste, bro.
This sesame paste is really good.
Even though I'm from Chongqing,
I also eat sesame paste.
When people from Chongqing eat hotpot...
They're not supposed to eat sesame paste, right?
There's no such...
There's no such rule.
Looks good.
It looks really good.
And it feels like your style once you put it on.
These things just...
Feel like when you wear them,
They gradually start to become yours.